<resources>
    <string name="app_name">30 Days App</string>
    <string name="andromeda_name">Andromeda – The Chained Maiden</string>
    <string name="andromeda_des">Andromeda is one of the Greek constellations. It was named after Andromeda, the daughter of Queen Cassiopeia and King Cepheus in Greek mythology. Andromeda was chained and left for the sea monster Cetus to eat, and then saved by Perseus, whom she later married.Andromeda was sacrificed to Cetus to appease the gods and stop the monster from ravaging her land. Cetus was sent by the god Poseidon after Cassiopeia had boasted that she was more beautiful than the nymphs.</string>
    <string name="apus_name">Apus – The Bird of Paradise</string>
    <string name="apus_des">Apus represents the bird of paradise. The constellation’s name means “no feet” in Greek, referring to a western misconception of the bird of paradise not having feet. The constellation was created and named by the Dutch astronomer and cartographer Petrus Plancius in the late 16th century.</string>
    <string name="aquarius_name">Aquarius – The Water Bearer</string>
    <string name="aquarius_des">Aquarius is one of the 48 Greek constellations. It is associated with Ganymede, the cup-bearer to the Olympian gods. In Greek mythology, Ganymede was the son of King Tros, known for giving the city of Troy its name. Ganymede was the most beautiful boy alive and Zeus was so infatuated with him that he took the form of an eagle and abducted the boy.In some versions of the myth, Zeus sent an eagle, represented by the constellation Aquila, to fetch Ganymede and bring him to Olympus.</string>
    <string name="aquila_name">Aquila – The Eagle</string>
    <string name="aquila_des">Aquila constellation is associated with the eagle that held Zeus’ thunderbolts in Greek mythology, as well as with the eagle that abducted Ganymede and brought him to Olympus.</string>
    <string name="ara_name">Ara – The Altar</string>
    <string name="ara_des">Ara represents the altar on which the gods formed an alliance before going to war with the Titans in Greek mythology. The gods were led by Zeus and the Titans by Atlas. It is said that Zeus placed the altar in the sky in honour of the gods’ victory. In various depictions of the constellation, the Milky Way represents the smoke rising from the altar.</string>
    <string name="aries_name">Aries – The Ram</string>
    <string name="aries_des">Aries is identified as the mythical winged ram with golden fleece that was sent by the nymph Nephele to save her son Phrixus after his father, King Athamas of Boeotia, had been given a false prophecy that he had to sacrifice his son to ward off famine. In the myth, Phrixus and his sister Helle climbed on the ram and were carried toward Colchis on the shore of the Black Sea. Helle lost her grip and fell into the Dardanelles on the way.The Greeks named the channel separating Europe and Asia the Hellerospont in her memory. The Golden Fleece was later the object of the Argonauts’ quest to Colchis.</string>
    <string name="auriga_name">Auriga – The Charioteer</string>
    <string name="auriga_des">Auriga, the Charioteer, was said to have been placed in the sky by Zeus himself in honour of the charioteer and inventor Erichthonius of Athens. Erichthonius was the son of the god Hephaestus and he was raised by Athena, who taught him many skills. He was the first person to harness four horses to a chariot and is credited as the inventor of the the quadriga, the four-horse chariot. His chariot was said to have been made in the image of the Sun god’s chariot.</string>
    <string name="caelum_name">Caelum – The Chisel</string>
    <string name="caelum_des">Caelum is one of the constellations created by Nicolas-Louis de Lacaille. Lacaille originally named the constellation Caelum Scalptorium (or les Burins in French), which is Latin for “the engraver’s chisel.”</string>

    <string name="camelopardalis_name">Camelopardalis – The Giraffe</string>
    <string name="camelopardalis_des">The Latin word camelopardalis means “the giraffe.” It is a combination of the Greek words for the camel and the leopard. The Greeks came up with the word because the giraffe had spots like a leopard and a long neck like a camel.</string>
    <string name="cancer_name">Cancer – The Crab</string>
    <string name="cancer_des">Cancer represents Karkinos, a crab sent by Hera to distract Heracles when he was fighting the Lemean Hydra as part of his Twelve Labours. In the myth, Heracles kicked the crab so hard that it flew all the way into the sky, where it became a constellation. In a different version of the myth, Heracles crushed the crab underfoot and Hera placed it into the sky.</string>
    <string name="carina_name">Carina – The Keel of Argo Navis</string>
    <string name="carina_des">Carina was one of the three constellations that formed Argo Navis, a large constellation that represented the ship Argo, on which Jason and the Argonauts sailed to Colchis to get the Golden Fleece. Argo Navis was divided into smaller constellations – Carina (the Keel), Puppis (the Stern) and Vela (the Sails) by Nicolas-Louis de Lacaille in the 18th century.</string>
    <string name="cassiopeia_name">Cassiopeia – The Queen</string>
    <string name="cassiopeia_des">Cassiopeia constellation represents the boastful queen Cassiopeia, wife of Cepheus and mother of Andromeda in Greek mythology. In the myth, Cassiopeia claimed that she was more beautiful than the Nereids. The nymphs asked the sea god Poseidon to punish the queen for her vanity. Poseidon sent the sea monster Cetus to ravage the queen’s land. King Cepheus asked an oracle for help and was told that he had to sacrifice his daughter Andromeda to appease Poseidon. The king and queen left their daughter chained to a rock, but Andromeda was saved from the monster by Perseus. Cassiopeia and Cepheus were placed into the sky by Poseidon. It is said that Cassiopeia spends six months every year upside down in the sky as punishment for her boastfulness.</string>
    <string name="cepheus_name">Cepheus – The King</string>
    <string name="cepheus_des">Cepheus constellation represents King Cepheus of Aethiopia (a region that contained parts of present-day Egypt, Jordan and Israel), husband of Cassiopeia and father of Andromeda. The constellations representing Cassiopeia, Andromeda and Perseus (who rescued Andromeda from the sea monster) lie in the same region of the sky.</string>
    <string name="coma_berenices_name">Coma Berenices – Berenice’s Hair</string>
    <string name="coma_berenices_des">Coma Berenices constellation was named after Queen Berenice II of Egypt (c. 266 – 221 BCE). Berenice swore to Aphrodite that she would cut off her long blonde hair if the goddess brought her husband, Ptolemy III Euergetes, back home safely from a dangerous mission against the Seleucids. When Ptolemy returned, the queen fulfilled her promise and placed her hair in Aphrodite’s temple. The hair disappeared the next day, which made the king angry. To calm him down, Conon, the court astronomer, told him that the goddess was so pleased with Berenice’s hair that she placed it into the sky.</string>
    <string name="cygnus_name">Cygnus – The Swan</string>
    <string name="cygnus_des">Cygnus constellation is most commonly associated with the myth of Leda, the Spartan queen who gave birth to two sets of twins – the mortal Clytemnestra and Castor and the immortal Pollux and Helen – after being seduced by Zeus, who came to her in the form of a swan. The mortal children were fathered by Leda’s husband Tyndareus and the immortal ones by Zeus. Castor and Pollux are associated with Gemini constellation.</string>
    <string name="draco_name">Draco – The Dragon</string>
    <string name="draco_des">Draco constellation represents the dragon Ladon, the mythical creature with a hundred heads that guarded the gardens of the Hesperides in Greek mythology. Heracles defeated the dragon with his poisoned arrows as part of his Twelve Labours. In Roman legend, Draco is associated with one of the Giant Titans who warred with Zeus and other Olympian gods for a decade. The Titan met his end at the hands of Minerva in battle and was thrown into the sky, where it froze around the North Pole.</string>
    <string name="equuleus_name">Equuleus – The Little Horse (Foal)</string>
    <string name="equuleus_des">Equuleus constellation is usually associated with Hippe, the daughter of the centaur Chiron. Hippe was seduced by Aeolus and became pregnant with his child, but was too ashamed to tell her father about the pregnancy. She hid from Chiron in the mountains and, when he came looking for her, she prayed to the gods that he didn’t find her. The gods granted her wish and turned her into a mare, represented by Equuleus constellation. Hippe is said to still be hiding from Chiron, with only her head showing behind Pegasus constellation.</string>
    <string name="eridanus_name">Eridanus – The River</string>
    <string name="eridanus_des">Eridanus is the ancient Greek name for the river Po in Italy. In mythology, Eridanus is usually associated with the story of Phaëton, the son of the Sun god Helios who begged his father to let him drive his chariot across the sky. Helios agreed to this and Phaëton mounted the chariot. However, since he was an inexperienced driver, he soon lost control of the horses and the chariot plunged close to Earth, setting lands on fire and turning Libya into a desert. Zeus had to prevent further tragedy and he struck the young man down with a thunderbolt. Phaëton fell into the river Eridanus and his father did not drive his chariot for days after his son’s passing, leaving the world in darkness.</string>
    <string name="gemini_name">Gemini – The Twins</string>
    <string name="gemini_des">Gemini constellation was named after the mythical twins Castor and Polydeuces. Two of the constellation’s brightest stars carry the twins’ names.</string>
    <string name="hercules_name">Hercules</string>
    <string name="hercules_des">Hercules constellation was named after Heracles, the legendary hero from Greek mythology. It is one of the oldest constellations in the sky, dating back to Sumerian times.</string>
    <string name="hydra_name">Hydra – The Water Serpent</string>
    <string name="hydra_des">The largest of the 88 constellations was named after the Lernaean Hydra, the monster from the myth of Heracles’ Twelve Labours. It is one of the Greek constellations, first documented by Ptolemy in the 2nd century.</string>
    <string name="libra_name">Libra – The Scales</string>
    <string name="libra_des">The name Libra means “the weighing scales” in Latin, and the constellation represents the scales of justice held by Dike, the Greek goddess of justice, associated with Virgo constellation.</string>
    <string name="lupus_name">Lupus – The Wolf</string>
    <string name="lupus_des">Lupus is a very old constellation, first catalogued by Ptolemy. It was not associated with the wolf until the Renaissance times. The Greeks called the constellation Therium, which means “wild animal,” and the Romans knew it as Bestia, the beast. The stars of Lupus used to be part of Centaurus constellation, and they represented an animal sacrificed by the centaur. The centaur was holding the animal toward an altar, represented by Ara constellation.</string>
    <string name="monoceros_name">Monoceros – The Unicorn</string>
    <string name="monoceros_des">The name Monoceros means “the unicorn” in Latin. The constellation was created by the Dutch astronomer, cartographer, and clergyman Petrus Plancius in 1612. He named it after the unicorn because the mythical animal appears several times in the Old Testament.</string>
    <string name="pegasus_name">Pegasus – The Winged Horse</string>
    <string name="pegasus_des">Pegasus represents the white winged horse from Greek mythology. The horse was said to have sprung from the neck of the Gorgon Medusa when Perseus beheaded her.</string>
    <string name="phoenix_name">Phoenix – The Firebird</string>
    <string name="phoenix_des">The constellation Phoenix represents the mythical firebird, sacred across many cultures and mythologies. Phoenix was one of the southern constellations introduced by Dutch explorers in the late 16th century.</string>
    <string name="pisces_name">Pisces – The Fish</string>
    <string name="pisces_des">Pisces is one of the zodiac constellations, first catalogued by Ptolemy along with the other Greek constellations. It is associated with a story about the goddess Aphrodite and her son Eros transforming into fish to escape the monster Typhon.</string>
    <string name="sagittarius_name">Sagittarius – The Archer</string>
    <string name="sagittarius_des">Sagittarius constellation represents a centaur aiming an arrow toward Antares, the bright star that marks the scorpion’s heart. It is also frequently associated with Crotus, the son of Pan, who invented archery and lived on Mount Helicon. Crotus was said to have two feet and a satyr’s tail. Sagittarius is also sometimes wrongly associated with the centaur Chiron, represented by Centaurus constellation.</string>
    <string name="vulpecula_name">Vulpecula – The Little Fox</string>
    <string name="vulpecula_des">Vulpecula constellation was created and named by the Polish astronomer Johannes Hevelius in the 17th century. It represents a little fox holding a goose in its jaws. Hevelius originally named it Vulpecula et Anser, which means “the little fox with the goose” in Latin. He said that the constellation represented a fox carrying a goose to Cerberus, the dog that guarded the entrance to the Underworld in Greek mythology.</string>

    <string name="day_1">Day 1</string>
    <string name="day_2">Day 2</string>
    <string name="day_3">Day 3</string>
    <string name="day_4">Day 4</string>
    <string name="day_5">Day 5</string>
    <string name="day_6">Day 6</string>
    <string name="day_7">Day 7</string>
    <string name="day_8">Day 8</string>
    <string name="day_9">Day 9</string>
    <string name="day_10">Day 10</string>
    <string name="day_11">Day 11</string>
    <string name="day_12">Day 12</string>
    <string name="day_13">Day 13</string>
    <string name="day_14">Day 14</string>
    <string name="day_15">Day 15</string>
    <string name="day_16">Day 16</string>
    <string name="day_17">Day 17</string>
    <string name="day_18">Day 18</string>
    <string name="day_19">Day 19</string>
    <string name="day_20">Day 20</string>
    <string name="day_21">Day 21</string>
    <string name="day_22">Day 22</string>
    <string name="day_23">Day 23</string>
    <string name="day_24">Day 24</string>
    <string name="day_25">Day 25</string>
    <string name="day_26">Day 26</string>
    <string name="day_27">Day 27</string>
    <string name="day_28">Day 28</string>
    <string name="day_29">Day 29</string>

</resources>